<_>
   <form_key>QGAY8sXEfRHBE9ok</form_key>
   <name>diglin_ricento</name>
   <channel>community</channel>
   <version_ids>
      <version_ids>2</version_ids>
   </version_ids>
   <summary>Sell your products from Magento to ricardo.ch and sync your order back into your shop to treat them.</summary>
   <description>&lt;h3&gt;Four easy steps: Install, Configure, Select your products, List &lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
			  &lt;p&gt;The Magento extension for ricardo.ch helps you easily to publish and sell your products on ricardo.ch marketplace offering you an additional stream of revenue.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;This extension replaces the ricardo assistant and deliver you the same features as this one but from your Magento shop, by synchronizing your Magento catalog to ricardo.ch. Orders passed on ricardo.ch are sent back to your shop, keeping all your orders in a unique place and making your daily business easier.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;With this extension, you can define a list of products to publish, set all payment and shipping rules supported by the ricardo.ch platform, choose the price variation and the type of sales (auction and/or direct sales), select the ricardo category where to publish, define product conditions or options to promote your products. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;The extension is quite flexible, allowing you to define the settings at products listing level or product listing item level. It offers you also the capability to publish your product data to the two supported ricardo.ch languages: german and french.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;Main Features&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;ul&gt;
				    &lt;li&gt;Synchronize and sell your products to ricardo.ch marketplace (Magento -&amp;gt; ricardo.ch)&lt;/li&gt;
                     &lt;li&gt;Create products listing to elaborate different sales options and rules&lt;/li&gt;
                     &lt;li&gt;Configuration of the sales options and rules at products listing or products level&lt;/li&gt;
                     &lt;li&gt;Add products to a products listing from selected categories or manual selection&lt;/li&gt;
                     &lt;li&gt;Support of Magento product types: simple, grouped and configurable&lt;/li&gt;
                     &lt;li&gt;Product data synchronization in French and/or German&lt;/li&gt;
                     &lt;li&gt;Support for Swiss Franc currency&lt;/li&gt;
                     &lt;li&gt;Pre-Check the product data and products listing configuration before to send to ricardo.ch&lt;/li&gt;
                     &lt;li&gt;Cleanup of listing/synchronization jobs/orders logs after a period of time automatically after 30 days or a customized period&lt;/li&gt;
                     &lt;li&gt;Preview before to list your products&lt;/li&gt;
                     &lt;li&gt;Create the orders passed on ricardo.ch into your Magento shop&lt;/li&gt;
                     &lt;li&gt;Merge orders of different articles from the same customer when he bought products in a period of 30min (Cross Selling)&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;Support&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;ul&gt;
					&lt;li&gt;Extension available on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.magentocommerce.com/magento-connect/magento-extension-for-ricardo-ch-by-diglin.html&quot;&gt;MagentoConnect&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/diglin/ricento&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://diglin.zendesk.com&quot;&gt;Documentation &amp;amp; FAQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;li&gt;Email support: support at diglin.com - fees may apply - contact us for more information&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;About ricardo.ch&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;With around 700,000 current offers (auctions and fixed price), 2.5 million brand-name articles on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ricardoshops&quot;&gt;ricardoshops&lt;/a&gt;.ch, around 100,000 vehicles plus 35,000 parts and accessories on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.autoricardo.ch&quot;&gt;autoricardo.ch&lt;/a&gt; and over 2.3 million members, ricardo.ch is the largest online marketplace in Switzerland. Every three minutes somebody buys an article on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ricardo.ch&quot;&gt;ricardo.ch&lt;/a&gt; using a mobile device. ricardo.ch AG employs over 140 people in Switzerland and is headquartered in Zug.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;About Diglin&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.diglin.com&quot;&gt;Diglin&lt;/a&gt; is the Swiss eCommerce Agency per excellence, realizing your eCommerce project with success. It will accompany along the whole life of your eCommerce project at any levels: conception, realization, design, marketing, logistic, data treatment and management, resource optimization, cost efficiency, increase in turnover, etc. Diglin concentrates its activities mainly with the solutions Magento (eCommerce), OroCRM (CRM) and Akeneo (PIM) and work with its partners highly qualified to provide you the best solutions regarding your needs. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
   <license>OSL v3.0</license>
   <license_uri>http://opensource.org/licenses/osl-3.0.php</license_uri>
   <version>1.0.14</version>
   <stability>stable</stability>
   <notes>## Version 1.0.14
Fix an issue revealed after fixes done in version 1.0.13 related to getting sales options and rules from products listing item during getting new orders

## Version 1.0.13
Important fix for price products (and sales options &amp; rules in general) when several listing processes running at same time

## Version 1.0.12
7485ad0 Prevent Exception while editing product if API problem appear while conditions options
2927622 Add translation for frontend, change payment info template
29069ea Fix wrong variable name for payment method instruction
1738457 add payment block info in frontend area too for email generated from backend
259f885 Fix issue with products grid and massaction
8d37514 Update readme file
ea18812 Redirect to edit page if error occur
0fe5a3c Implement Bank information display if ricardo.ch payment method Bank transfer is used, Remove the cleanup listing log as it is duplicate with the job cleanup
9cd82a8 Change order of the tab display 1) Synchronization 2) Listing Log instead of the opposite
bc809c0 Fix random security error message on fresh install

## Version 1.0.10
e2304ab Change the status of an item to stop if the item has not been sold. It will stop the complete list if all items are stopped.
e2c0676 Set website Id while saving new customer even if store id was also provided to be sure that the user is saved into the correct website
0d01b4a Fix missing log url in message
ff1005c Skip required option when creating an order, also for custom option
9b48ef6 Fix missing home number

## Version 1.0.9
- Fix issue with some optional API property set to 0 (like template Id)
- 0c1eb42 Revert temporary success / error in dispatcher list , improve translations of string in product grid
- 74c3284 Show a small message in sync grid while running or chunk running to allow to differentiate both kind of sync
- 68eed7f Raise to 400 items to trigger in dispatch
- 1d3a839 Prevent create a new job while having a chunk running sync list
- 3241ef0 Change the way to handle the bucket of items in the dispatcher, fix a bug while triggering the order dispatcher and getting the list of listed items
- adcbc59 Improve message display in sync grid
- 6b6c45e Fix issue with &quot;Until Sold&quot; feature
- 2f48ea4 Improve the way to set/get successful or error log item
- 86fcc17 Display Product list name in the sync log grid instead to put it as message
- 1219b09 Fix issue with products grid and configurable products having article inserted also as simple article
- 95efdca Fix duplicate collection item error
- 4d38ed3 Make the option Schedule Reactivation &quot;Until Sold&quot; better explicit and working
- 03bc9cd Update code documentation
- 658c9f6 In some cases, picture&apos;s extension is not recognized so change the logic to determine if it exists or not Catch Exception and log them in cron class
## Version 1.0.8
- b5f1afa Update translations file
- c0d3fbb Fix issue with dispatcher and completed status
- 27c48c9 Fix interface issue (invisible language was also required input) with language selection and payment method &quot;other&quot; which needs a payment description and shipping description field if shipping &quot;other&quot; is selected
- 9e0be11 Improve debugging content when dispatcher mets errors
- b994fa0 Improve grid translations for products
- 84baa1b Change order of token DEV/PROD configuration fields
- 868e576 Fix issue with product price max limit (should be only for &quot;Buy now&quot; and payment method with credit card)
- 379a51b Fix issue with too long strings saved into DB if error occurred
- 0eb9f8d Cosmetic code changes
- 79ce926 Change translation
- 356c909 Fix issue with job message and json encoding (some loop appeared in some use cases)
- 738f316 Better judge if some values must be retrieved from the API depending if the extension is configured or not
- cd34d94 Prevent loop when doing the dispatch
- 14d3beb fix uninstall file txt with wrong language folder package
- a5e6350 Fix translation issue in the sync grid
- 90a2f7c Fix issue if extension is disabled with payment and shipping methods
- 33055cc Add nl2br for description

## Version 1.0.7
- 42f18da Prevent warning messages for some variables, Prevent Exception when picture doesn&apos;t exist in preview, set per default the dev mode to 1 because user receives BETA API Token first and some people doesn&apos;t set correctly the configuration
- 29767d9 Add more condition to display error in case of wrong API configuration and coming from banner notification
- 57da567 Invite user to check his configuration if a problem occurs
- c514cb0 Merge branch &apos;develop&apos;
 
## Version 1.0.6
- 6a6ca4f Do not set the status of the parent configurable product when list on ricardo.ch
- eb0d25a Handle correctly errors if done in the backend notification banner
- 68f812a add short description as fallback product description
- bb0c931 change redirect url and add error message
- c4fbe49 Check and List action: save also product listing information
- 349218a Merge branch &apos;develop&apos; of git://github.com/diglin/ricento into develop
- f467eb4 Fix issue with grid of products after filter reset (missing form key hidden field)
- 4cc8e3b Revert changes done for RIC-102, display products item w/o any error
- afb9215 Add new url to register to the API
- c0b50e9 In case errors are coming from the API but it is at backend notification level, we catch the error and display it as session error message
- 7d0c803 Merge branch &apos;develop&apos; of github.com:diglin/ricento into develop
- 068a409 allow to delete a job even if it is running, fix some typo translations, allow to save when clicking on &quot;check and list&quot; button from a product listing

## Version 1.0.5
- c1b3c90 Merge branch &apos;develop&apos;
- 9f59a2f Fix definitely issue RIC-102 with product grid display
- 3c3547a Fix issue RIC-102: product grid display in product listing with some configuration provide error cause of the collection and duplicate items found
- 5d1706e Merge pull request #1 from diglin/develop

## Version 1.0.4
- ebaec62 Remove the filter collection to not get &quot;not visible&quot; products. Don&apos;t remember the reason of this filter, hope it doesn&apos;t have consequence with order creation (normally no)
- 90e2a93 Merge branch &apos;develop&apos;

## Version 1.0.3
- c55a6dd Fix issue with wrong store id, should not be website id while getting storeConfig
- 00c2960 Update README.md

## Version 1.0.2
- 880dbfd Fix issue if API not yet configured and Product Edit Page is requested from the backend
- 5841d06 Update gitsubmodule (replace bitbucket with github)
- be2b77a Update readme file
- 9384e3c Update doc
</notes>
   <authors>
      <name>
         <name>diglin</name>
      </name>
      <user>
         <user>diglin</user>
      </user>
      <email>
         <email>sly@diglin.com</email>
      </email>
   </authors>
   <depends_php_min>5.3.2</depends_php_min>
   <depends_php_max>5.6.0</depends_php_max>
   <depends>
      <package>
         <name>
            <name/>
         </name>
         <channel>
            <channel/>
         </channel>
         <min>
            <min/>
         </min>
         <max>
            <max/>
         </max>
         <files>
            <files>                             </files>
         </files>
      </package>
      <extension>
         <name>
            <name>Core</name>
         </name>
         <min>
            <min/>
         </min>
         <max>
            <max/>
         </max>
      </extension>
   </depends>
   <contents>
      <target>
         <target>magelocal</target>
         <target>mageetc</target>
         <target>magedesign</target>
         <target>magedesign</target>
         <target>magedesign</target>
         <target>mageskin</target>
         <target>magecommunity</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
         <target>mageweb</target>
         <target>magelib</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
      </target>
      <path>
         <path/>
         <path>modules/Diglin_Ricento.xml</path>
         <path>adminhtml/default/default/layout/ricento.xml</path>
         <path>adminhtml/default/default/template/ricento</path>
         <path>frontend/base/default/template/ricento</path>
         <path>adminhtml/default/default/ricento</path>
         <path>Diglin/Ricento</path>
         <path>en_US/Diglin_Ricento.csv</path>
         <path>en_US/template/email/ricento</path>
         <path>fr_FR/Diglin_Ricento.csv</path>
         <path>fr_FR/template/email/ricento</path>
         <path>js/ricento</path>
         <path>Diglin/Ricardo</path>
         <path>de_DE/Diglin_Ricento.csv</path>
         <path>de_DE/template/email/ricento</path>
         <path>de_CH/Diglin_Ricento.csv</path>
         <path>de_CH/template/email/ricento</path>
      </path>
      <type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
      </type>
      <include>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
      </include>
      <ignore>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore>#^.svn|.git|.DS_Store#</ignore>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore>#^.svn|.git|.DS_Store#</ignore>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore>#^.svn|.git|.DS_Store#</ignore>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore>#^.svn|.git|.DS_Store#</ignore>
         <ignore>#^.svn|.git|.DS_Store#</ignore>
         <ignore>#^.svn|.git|.DS_Store#</ignore>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore>#^.svn|.git|.DS_Store#</ignore>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore>#^.svn|.git|.DS_Store#</ignore>
         <ignore/>
      </ignore>
   </contents>
</_>
